TAHA CHAGHTAI

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

SKILLS

HTML5
CSS3 - SCSS
Javascript
React.JS
Redux
Bootstrap 4-5
Material UI
Tailwind
Next.js
WordPress
CMS
Axios
FrameWork motion
Asp.net Web Api (Basics)

CONTACT

+971 589774082 taha.chaghtai.dev@gmail.com

SOCIAL LINKS

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/taha - chaghtai-029b7017a/

GITHUB

https://github.com/Taha-0697

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: 06-11-1997 **Nationality:** Pakistani

Religion: Islam

CNIC: 42101-2597380-7

PROFILE:

A young and promising Web Developer, specializing in front end development who has experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. I am well-versed in numerous programming languages including JavaScript, React Js, Next Js, WordPress, Php, Laravel and others.

EXPERIENCE:

Super Stamp March 2022 - Present

Working as a Frontend Developer where I have developed and managed Websites on different platforms. Currently, I am working on c# .net core Mvc and JavaScript Frameworks / Libraries i.e: React Js , Next Js.

Al-Tafseer Solution Aug 2021 - Feb 2022

Have worked as a Frontend Developer and developed and managed Websites on different platforms such as Wordpress opensources and JavaScript Frameworks / Libraries i.e: React Js , Next Js.

The Digital Hands Jan 2021 - July 2021

Have worked as a CMS Developer and developed and managed WordPress websites. I started as an internee which further led to the job , At The Digital Hands I have experienced building Custom CMS Websites as well as Theme BasedWebsites ie. PHp Laravel WordPress

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

SUPER STAMP

Super stamp is a loyalty program across UAE and QATAR its an application where user will get stamps and Loyalty Offers as reward.

THE CORE DESING

The Core Design is a Web for Branding and for Freelancing, (https://thecoredesigns.com)

Jobs Middle East

Jobs Middle East is a job Portal for Job Seekers and Companies

URBXN CENTRAL

UrbxnCentral is an events managemnt system

SUPER AUTO GROUP

Cars Inventory System

SUPER STAMP ADMIN PORTAL

Super stamp admin is a web for Merchants to set offers and discounts for customers

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S OF COMPUTER SCIENCE — BS (CS)

Iqra University | 2018 - 2021

INTERMEDIATE (Comput Science)

Gulshan College | 2015-2017